FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
Man! Well, it's a good thing that Ryu
just happened to know where Kazehaya had
- disappeared to!
- Well... I was just talking to
him. Oh, really? And about what?
Can't say.
Seriously?!
I think she was
misunderstood... more than she wasn't.
She kept her feelings
inside... more than she expressed.
But I like the Kuronuma who
gives it her all regardless.
I also... don't want to give up.
I like her.
I want him to know.
Please...
This time...
Reach him!
Ryu?
Kuronuma...
I'm shaking... I can't stop.
The time to tell Kazehaya... all
of the feelings I've kept inside...
is now!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you cry.
I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble.
And I'm sorry... for saying
things... without thinking.
If you ever want to tell me something,
Then please do.
I'll listen. No matter what it might be.
Because my feelings for
you will never change.
Yeah.
My "like" and your "like"
are probably different.
Looking for Yoshida and
Yano? They're outside.
No, I... I'm actually here to see you!
I have something to say...
Something I really need you to know.
Stay there. Okay?
It's fine.
Let's stay like this.
I want you to hear this.
Kazehaya...
Until now... whenever I did anything around
other people, no matter what it was, they
would always apologize to me.
That's why... the first day
of school... when I met you...
...to be honest... it made me really
happy... You smiled at me... and thanked me.
I never was just was
just "treating you fairly"
But still...
It made me so happy.
It felt like... everything lit up in color.
Kazehaya... had transformed my entire world.
Just his existence alone...
changed how I lived life day by day.
But I...realized...
That I was doing the exact
opposite... of what you had done for me.
Now I know... that it's time...
... so instead of "I'm Sorry" hear this...
Thank you for smiling at me.
Thank you for talking to me.
Thank you for being so kind to me.
And also... for making me experience so many
feelings I never knew before... Thank you.
No.
- Kuronuma...
- I like you!
I like you!
I like you. I like you.
I like you.
I can't possibly convey...
...all the things that I'm feeling.
How do I put them into
words?... It's overwhelming.
I simply... like you.
A lot.
I really...
...like you.
No, please! Don't open
it! R-Right now, I'm...
I'm... too embarrassed... to show my face.
I wonder... if Sawako was
able to talk with him.
Dunno. you good if we
just head home for now?
Kazehaya! Hey, Kazehaya! If you're
around, c'mon, raise your hand up!
Think they'll be okay?!
Yeah, they're gonna be
alright. Plus, Ryu's here.
Oh... Ryu! Y'know where Kazehaya is?
So did you hear me?
Hello?
- You sure about that?
- Hey! Ryu! -You know he's the
- type that can't help but be honest.
- You know where he is, right?
Yeah... But at least he's just
dealing with idiot Joe. He'll be fine.
- Ya know, your best buddy?
- Oh, hey, it's you two. Got
any clue where Kuronuma is?
- Uh no we don't!
- Huh? Well, that's
absolutely no help at all!
What do you need? We can
give her a message for you.
Nah, I can tell I won't
get anywhere with you guys.
Hold on I just thought of something good.
I can't wait.
- This is gonna be a problem!
Then Bet she'll be near the classroom.
Oh right! She went home!
- Yeah! She's outta here!
- Then why wouldn't you just
- tell me that in the first place?
- W-We forgot!
- She totally went home already!
- Uh-huh! She's long gone!
Oh yeah, the classroom.
K-Kuronuma...
I... I-I... I-
Wait!
Don't look away.
And look at me.
It feels...
Like it's been way too long... since I was
able... to actually look you in the eyes.
Oh! So, there you are,
I finally found you.
Sadako's here too? Pin's looking for ya.
Sounded like it was kinda urgent too. So
anyway guys, what were you both up to?
What... were we up to?
That's a... good question...
Kuro--
- I-I'm getting called by the teacher...
- Honestly, what was I doing?!
Kuronuma!
Kazehaya! Hey, what were you doing?
I've been looking everywhere for you!
What was I doing-?
Man...
What?
I was having an important talk!
Oh? Yeah?
Well, that doesn't really matter to me,
but yeah so for when we meet up to eat our
snacks later whaddaya think about a 7030
split between salty and sweet? Or are you
more of an 8020 kinda guy
cause me I definitely think...
Yeah I don't care!
You screwed up?!
Be careful! If you're gonna mess
up then do it to the guys' costumes!
Sounds good! Yeah, we should
just try and keep it to Joe's!
- ... But, you did confess to him, right?
- Uh Well maybe I sorta did.
What does that even
mean? Give us the deets girl!
W-when it came down to it, I couldn't
even tell him a tenth of what I really
- wanted to say.
- So, what did he say after that?
"Say"?
Wha...
- What'd he... do?
"Do"!
U-Uh... um...
Heeeeey!
- What the heck are you doing here?!
- Well, right back at you!
What reason could you
possibly have for coming here?!
I'm such a caring
homeroom teacher, aren't I?
I wanted to talk to Kuronuma a
little bit... about tomorrow's performance.
I... I totally forgot.
- You can just save that for tomorrow!
- Why did my mom have to let him in?
I came up with a brilliant idea. Something
that'll definitely win over the hearts of
the judges. -Kuronuma,
come here a sec. -A-Alright!
And that heavy looking bag he brought
with him doesn't even have treats in it
- for us?
- He's definitely got
some kinda bet going again!
Look, he has ulterior motives
written all over his stupid face!
U-Ulterior motives?!
Let's get down to business. So, about
tomorrow's costume march. When it's time
for you to do your solo
performance... ...use this...
I... Well...
There's no way I can look at Kazehaya
anymore without having any ulterior
motiiiiiiives!
G-Good for you.
No it's not at alllll!
Cause he said that his feelings for me
will never change. So now, I don't know
what to do. It's only if there's a
chance... If there's a chance, then I-I-I-I...
Listen, you think that Shota or literally
any other dude out there... doesn't have at
least some ulterior motives?
They do!
They're natural and from the heart!
So now that we've settled that... Tomorrow,
make sure to put each of these things on
the judges' plates, okay?
... Just one at a time.
- Uh-huh!
- Remember, ulterior
motives are natural to have!
Right.
Also... everything you just said? Make
sure to tell that directly to his face
tomorrow. 'kay?
Otherwise, it'll keep being a huge pain.
Now. Adios!
I will!
Huh... Just now... Didn't I kinda say
something like really extremely awesome?
That's it! I gotta head over
to Shota's place right away!
- You got enough paint over there?
- Yeah.
- I don't think we're gonna make it.
- I can't see any way we could.
An all-nighter, huh...
- the girls said Pin came over.
- To Yoshida's?
Yup. They said we should
look at the "Pin Raid Forecast."
A "Pin Raid Alert's" more like it, huh?
Yeah, no doubt.
There's no reason he
needs to come over here.
He's probably just lonely!
- Gonna use the bathroom real quick.
- Kay.
Yo! How's it goin', Mr.
Ulterior Motives Guy!
- Go home!
- Seriously? I came all the way over here
to educate you on how ulterior motives are
natural!
- Whatever, leave!]
- W-What do you think you're doing?
Listen up, y'all! Your friend Shota
here's a little perve! His head's full of
- ulterior motives!
- That's enough, go home.
- That's Pin.
- Kazehaya?
- Ulterior Motives!
- Ulterior motives?
Hey, Shota! I went out of my way to come
here and tell you something awesome! You
should be grateful! Touched even!
Thankin' me with a twinkle in your eye,
dammit!
- Ugh, will we make it in time?
- Oh yeah! We got this!
Hey, the guys said that Pin
came over to their place too!
No way! I guess he got
locked out and is throwing a fit!
Then, it's a good thing he didn't
stick around here for too long!
- Nerve-racking...
- Sawako, when do you
get to talk to him next?
- Exciting...
- Mmm, I-I think... Before the parade.
You can do it!
Anxiety inducing...
I can't wait for tomorrow to
come... when did I last feel like this?
So Kazehaya, what's with
that "ulterior motives" thing?
Hey man, that's what I wanna know!
I think Pin's hobby is
messing with you, for real!
Hey Joe hasn't done
anything but eat snacks.
Do you guys think Ryu
is ever gonna wake up?
TO: SAWAKO KURONUMA
LET'S TALK ONCE MORE
Hurry...
- I want to see you.
If it's the two of us... surely...
If we're together... we'll have more...
Next time: "From Now on"